qualitybux.com 2009-09-13

# QualityBux : Privacy Policy

\- QualityBux.com asks for some personal information when you create an QualityBux.com Account, including your username, and password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. An QualityBux.com Account allows you to access certain QualityBux.com services that require registration.  
\- When you use QualityBux.com, QualityBux.com's servers automatically record certain information about your use of QualityBux.com. Similar to other web services, QualityBux.com records information such as account activity (including number of log-ins), data displayed or clicked on (including UI elements, ads, links); and other log information (including browser type, IP-address, country location, date and time of access, cookie ID, and referrer URL).  
\- QualityBux.com Cookies - When you visit QualityBux.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some QualityBux.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled (ie. An QualityBux.com user account requires that cookies are enabled).  

QualityBux.com is not responsible for any of the contents in advertisements shown at QualityBux.com. This applies to all advertisement information we may display. It's your responsibility when you click an advertisement link, click a link inside the advertisement page or browse the advertisement contents. All advertisements are the responsibility of its advertiser and you must comply to their own Terms of Service and Privacy Policies. 

When you send email or other communication to QualityBux.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

\- We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
\- We restrict access to personal information to QualityBux.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.  

\- QualityBux.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

This agreement can change. Although we have the right to change this agreement without any prior notice to our members, we will send out a notice to all of our members the new terms and/or terms that have changed changed. If for any reason you do not accept the changes, you will need to contact us, and your account will be removed.
